A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21 FA242
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Hugh Morrow, Series 21
1958-1977
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
Morrow, Hugh
FA242
42 Cubic Feet 107 document boxes
Arrangement
These papers are organized into the following 6 subseries:
1. General Files; 2. Campaign Files, Presidential; 3. Campaign Files, 1970 Gubernatorial; 4. Speech Transcripts; 5. Vice Presidential Press Releases; 6. Subject Files.
Scope and Contents note
NOTE TO RESEARCHERS
This collection contains the office files of Hugh Morrow. The files document the official activities of Hugh Morrow in the execution of his duties as a member of Nelson A. Rockefeller's gubernatorial and vice presidential staff. The actions, decisions, exchanges of information, and points of view documented occurred in the course of proposing and implementing policies of the Rockefeller administration, political campaigns, or personal activities. However, unless a document is specifically addressed to or from Nelson A. Rockefeller, or is referred to in a document addressed to him, it should not be assumed that he saw the document or was aware of its existence or substance. Furthermore, researchers should keep in mind that staff files may contain documents or drafts addressed to Rockefeller that were never shown to him.
This collection documents portions of Nelson A. Rockefeller's public life from 1958 to 1977. Hugh Morrow was a member of the executive staff during Rockefeller's terms as Governor of New York and subsequently U.S. Vice President.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
This collection was donated to the Rockefeller Archive Center in 2004.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 21.2
Conditions Governing Access note
Collection is open for scholarly research with the following conditions: All archival material in the Rockefeller family collections that provides the names, correspondence, or activities of living members of the Rockefeller family, and/or documents the net worth of any Rockefeller family members, is restricted from public access.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Assembly and Senate Memos (FA354)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer) (FA366)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Press Office (FA368)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Departmental Reports (FA370)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Speeches (FA372)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Diane Van Wie (FA373)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Materials requiring specialized equipment for access (film, audio, video, slides) may be closed to research dependent on availability of the applicable equipment
Brittle or damaged items, or materials otherwise in need of preservation care, may be closed to researchers at the discretion of the RAC Head of Archival Services/Head of Reference.
Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Political campaigns -- United States; Presidential campaigns -- United States; New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller); Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich); Morrow, Hugh
- General Files, 1960-1974; 1; 20.4 Cubic Feet 50 document boxes
  Scope and Contents
  This subseries contains miscellaneous files on state and national issues.
  - Abortion, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture, National, 1962-1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture, National, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Agriculture, State, 1961-1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Aged (See also Health), 1960-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Aged, Meeting: Mentally Ill and Aged, 1972 August 15 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Albany South Mall Progress Report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Albany South Mall Progress Report, DRAFT, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Albany South Mall Audit Report, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Message, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1961-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Annual Message to Legislature, 1950-1973 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Articles Prepared for Possible Publication, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Articles Prepared for Possible Publication, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Articles Prepared for Possible Publication, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Articles, Statements, Forwarded Messages by Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Articles, Miscellaneous Requests and Correspondence, 1969-1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Athletic Commission, 1960-1962 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Atomic Research Development, 1960-1970 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Awareness Campaign, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Awareness Campaign Continued, Drafts and Revisions, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Awareness Campaign, Notes, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - "A" Miscellaneous, 1962-1964 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Bailey, Harry, 1964-1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Baird, Dr. Robert (See Narcotics), 1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Banking, 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Beauty Program (New York), 1965 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Bergenheim, Bob, NYC Newspaper, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Biaggi, Mario, 1961-1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    Conditions Governing Access note
    Restricted material
  - Biaggi, Mario, 1959 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Bill Signing, Correspondence, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Blacks in State Government, 1970-1972 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Bobich, Gica, 1961-1972 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Boorstin, Daniel (The Image), 1972 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Books, Inventory, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Bond Issues, New York State, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Budget, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Budget, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Budget, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1961-1969 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Budget: 1972 Message, (Working Papers) (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Budget: Nelson A. Rockefeller Letters to Students of C.U.NY, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Buffalo, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Bursten, Martin (see Human Rights), 1970-1974 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Business, Small, Nelson A. Rockefeller Statements, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Busing, 1969-1975 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Braun & Co., 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Brown, Harold, 1973-1975 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - "B" Miscellaneous, 1959-1974 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - California vs New York, 1962-1973 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Campaign Finance, Politics, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  - Campbell, Rodney, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - Campbell, Rodney, "Dear Mr. President"
    - Chapter 1. Western Europe, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Chapter 2. Russia, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Chapter 3. East-West Trade, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Chapter 4. North Atlantic Community, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Chapter 5. The Middle East, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Chapter 6. Africa, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Chapter 7. Southeast Asia, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Chapter 8. China, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Chapter 9. Northeast Asia, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Chapter 10. Latin America, Mexico, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Chapter 11. Latin America, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Chapter 12. United Nations, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Chapter 13. International Monetary Fund, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Chapter 14. Food and Population, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - Chapter 15. Sea and Space, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 58)
  - Carberry, Jim, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 59)
  - Carey, Hugh, 1874-1975 (Box 6, Folder 60)
  - Chapin, Roger, (see also Veteran: POW'S), 1973 (Box 6, Folder 61)
  - Case, Gene, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 62)
  - Chapman, Bruce, 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 63)
  - Childs, Marquis, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - Civil Disorders (Memo of Understanding, NYS-NYC), 1970 (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Civil Rights (See Also Human Rights), 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Civil Service, 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Civil Service, 1959-1971 (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Commerce Department (New York State), 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 69)
  - Commerce Department (New York State), 1969-1971 (Box 6, Folder 70)
  - Commerce Department (New York State), 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 71)
  - Commerce, International Division, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 72)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 73)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, 1973-1974 (Box 7, Folder 74)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, Notes, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 75)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, Binder, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 76)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, Dinner, 1973 December 3 (Box 7, Folder 77)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, New York City Announcement, 1973 November 18 (Box 7, Folder 78)
  - Commission on Critical Choices, Report, Origin: Role of Modern State in the Changing World, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 79)
  - Communications (Miscellaneous), 1963-1972 (Box 7, Folder 80)
  - Communism, 1961-1964 (Box 8, Folder 81)
  - Community Development, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 82)
  - Confederations of States, 1954-1962 (Box 8, Folder 83)
  - John Connally, Occidental Oil, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 84)
  - Professor Connery, Rehabilitation Facilities, 1969-1974 (Box 8, Folder 85)
  - Conservation, State Council, 1962-1970 (Box 8, Folder 86)
  - Constitutional Convention, New York State, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 87)
  - Constitutional Amendments Campaign, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 88)
  - Construction Fund State University, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 89)
  - Consumer Protection, 1960-1971 (Box 8, Folder 90)
  - Crime, New York State, Crime Control Issues, 1964-1969 (Box 8, Folder 91)
  - "C" Miscellaneous, 1959-1973 (Box 8, Folder 92)
  - Davies, Aled, American Meat Institute, 1960-1974 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Defense, 1961-1965 (Box 9, Folder 94)
  - Defense, 1959-1960 (Box 9, Folder 95)
  - Defense, National Security, (ABM), 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 96)
  - Defense, Nuclear Testing, 1959-1963 (Box 9, Folder 97)
  - Defense, Fallout Shelters, 1960-1962 (Box 9, Folder 98)
  - Defense, McHugh Report, "Survival in a Nuclear Attack", 1960 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Defense, Ruebhausen Report, "Protection from Radioactive Fallout", 1959 (Box 9, Folder 100)
  - Defense, Scrivner Report, "Public Reaction to the 1959-1960 Fallout Shelter Proposal", 1961, 1959-1960 1961 (Box 9, Folder 101)
  - Defense, Shelter Designs, Institute of Public Administration, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 102)
  - Defense, Nelson A. Rockefeller Nuclear Testing Statement, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 103)
  - Defense, Nelson A. Rockefeller Nuclear Testing Statement, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 104)
  - Defense, "No Test Ban Now" Statement, 1961 (Box 10, Folder 105)
  - Defense, "The Problem of Arms and Arms Control" Statement, 1960 (Box 10, Folder 106)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 October (Box 10, Folder 107)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 September (Box 10, Folder 108)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 August (Box 10, Folder 109)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 July (Box 10, Folder 110)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 June (Box 10, Folder 111)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 May (Box 10, Folder 112)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 April (Box 10, Folder 113)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 March (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 February (Box 10, Folder 115)
  - Delphis Hanover (New York Series) Domestic Economic Problems Digest of Data, 1973 January (Box 10, Folder 116)
  - Duckett. Al, (African-American Writer), Advisor to Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1972-1977 (Box 10, Folder 117)
  - Duckett. Al, (African-American Writer), Advisor to Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1969-1971 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Duckett. Al, (African-American Writer), Advisor the Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 119)
  - Duckett. Al, (African-American Writer), Advisor the Nelson A. Rockefeller, 1962-1963 (Box 11, Folder 120)
  - "D" Miscellaneous, 1960-1973 (Box 11, Folder 121)
  - Eckhof, William, Recommendations for Commissioner of Motor Vehicles, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 122)
  - Economics, Balance of Payments (Gold Drain), 1963-1971 (Box 11, Folder 123)
  - Economic Growth, 1964-1971 (Box 11, Folder 124)
  - Economic Growth, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 125)
  - Economic Growth, 1964-1969 (Box 11, Folder 126)
  - Economic Growth, 1963 (Box 12, Folder 127)
  - Economic Growth, 1960-1962 (Box 12, Folder 128)
  - Economic Growth, (Corporations), 1961-1972 (Box 12, Folder 129)
  - Economic Growth, (Council of Economic Advisors), 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folder 130)
  - Economic Growth, (Inflation), 1969 (Box 12, Folder 131)
  - Economic Growth, (Nelson A. Rockefeller Speeches, Clippings), 1962-1968 (Box 12, Folder 132)
  - Education, 1971-1973 (Box 12, Folder 133)
  - Education, 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 134)
  - Education, 1959-1960 (Box 12, Folder 135)
  - Education, (Academic Freedom and Policies), Loyalty Oath Statements, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Education, Decentralization, 1969 (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - Education, Higher Education, (SUNY), 1960-1973 (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Education, Parochial School Aid, 1971 (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Education, Policy Alternatives Institute in SUNY, 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - Education, Student Disorders (Bill), 1969 (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - Elections, General, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - Elections, (Law, Funding, Campaign Organization), 1973-1974 (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - Energy Crisis, (Gas Shortage, Oil, etc), 1973-1976 (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - Evans-Novak Report (Politics), 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - Evans-Novak Report (Politics), 1972-1973 (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - Environment, Miscellaneous, 1971-1972 (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Environment, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - Environment, Miscellaneous, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Environment, Department of Conservation, 1973 (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Environment, Department of Conservation, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - Environment, Department of Conservation, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - Environment, Department of Conservation, 1970 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Environment, National Commission on Water Quality, 1974 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Environment, National Commission on Water Quality, 1974 (Box 15, Folder 155)
  - NO FOLDER (Box 15, Folder 156)
  - Environment, National Commission on Water Quality, Resumes, 1973 (Box 15, Folder 157)
  - Environmental Conservation: New York State Waters, Water Pollution, 1964-1972 (Box 15, Folder 158)
  - "E" Miscellaneous, 1966-1968 (Box 15, Folder 159)
  - Federalism, Correspondence with Clarence Streit, 1970-1973 (Box 15, Folder 160)
  - Federalism, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965 1972 (Box 15, Folder 161)
  - Federalism, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962-1964 (Box 15, Folder 162)
  - Federalism, Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 163)
  - Federalism, Updating Goodkin and other Projects, 1971-1972 (Box 16, Folder 164)
  - Federalist Papers, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 165)
  - Federalism, Future of: Paperback Edition, 1963-1974 (Box 16, Folder 166)
  - Federalism, Future of: Paperback Edition, Three Copies, 1963-1974 (Box 16, Folder 167)
  - Films, 1965-1975 (Box 16, Folder 168)
  - Finkelstein, Jerry, 1973-1974 (Box 16, Folder 169)
  - Fiscal Integrity, 1963-1972 (Box 16, Folder 170)
  - Flowers, James, (Free-lance Writer), 1969-1974 (Box 16, Folder 171)
  - Ford Speech, National Press Club, 1965 March 25 (Box 16, Folder 172)
  - Foreign Affairs, Miscellaneous, 1963-1974 (Box 16, Folder 173)
  - Foreign Affairs, Miscellaneous, 1959-1962 (Box 17, Folder 174)
  - Foreign Affairs, Cambodia, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 175)
  - Foreign Affairs, China-Nixon Trip, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 176)
  - Foreign Affairs, Cuba, 1960-1973 (Box 17, Folder 177)
  - Foreign Affairs, Europe, 1963-1969 (Box 17, Folder 178)
  - Foreign Affairs, Germany (Berlin), 1961-1966 (Box 17, Folder 179)
  - Foreign Affairs, Israel, 1967-1972 (Box 17, Folder 180)
  - Foreign Affairs, Israel, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 180A)
  - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 1963-1973 (Box 17, Folder 181)
  - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 1960-1962 (Box 17, Folder 182)
  - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, 1959-1960 (Box 17, Folder 183)
  - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, Quality of Life in the Americas, Report of the U.S. Presidential Mission for the Western Hemisphere, 1969 August (Box 17, Folder 184)
  - Foreign Affairs, Latin America, Institute of Inter-American Affairs, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 185)
  - Foreign Affairs, Middle East Speeches, 1966-1970 (Box 18, Folder 186)
  - Foreign Affairs, NATO, 1962-1971 (Box 18, Folder 187)
  - Foreign Affairs, Russia (Wheat Sales) and Miscellaneous, 1962-1970 (Box 18, Folder 188)
  - Foreign Affairs, Southeast Asia (Vietnam), 1964-1968 (Box 18, Folder 189)
  - Foreign Affairs, Soviet Jews, 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 190)
  - Flower, George, (Book: The Negro and the Republican Party), 1966-1967 (Box 18, Folder 191)
  - Free, Lloyd, (Campaign Files, Polls, and Politics), 1971-1973 (Box 18, Folder 192)
  - Freedom of the Press, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 193)
  - Freedom of the Press, 1970-1972 (Box 19, Folder 194)
  - "F" Miscellaneous, 1963-1974 (Box 19, Folder 195)
  - Gervasi, Frank, Press Secretary, 1963-1965 (Box 19, Folder 196)
  - Gilhooley, John, Transit Authority, 1964-1968 (Box 19, Folder 197)
  - Goldwater, Barry, (Presidential Nominations), 1973 (Box 19, Folder 198)
  - Goodell, Charles E. (Congressman and Senator NYS Succeeded Robert F. Kennedy), 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 199)
  - Goodell, Charles E. (Congressman and Senator NYS Succeeded Robert F. Kennedy), 1969-1970 (Box 19, Folder 200)
  - Governors National Association, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 201)
  - Governorship, (Filmstrip by Guidance Associates), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 202)
  - Governorship, (Filmstrip by Guidance Associates), 1968 (Box 19, Folder 203)
  - Government, (Federal, State, Local), Federal Aid, 1966 (Box 19, Folder 204)
  - Government, (Local), 1961-1972 (Box 20, Folder 205)
  - Government, (Reorganization of Executive Branch, Nelson A. Rockefeller Proposal), 1960 (Box 20, Folder 206)
  - Guylay, Lou, (Political Campaign, Public Relations), 1970-1977 (Box 20, Folder 207)
  - "G" Miscellaneous, 1960-1973 (Box 20, Folder 208)
  - Harlem Office Building, 1969-1970 (Box 20, Folder 209)
  - Hatzes, George A. Jr., (Free Enterprise and Small Business), 1965 (Box 20, Folder 210)
  - Health Insurance (Universal), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 211)
  - Health (Medical Care for the Aged), 1962-1972 (Box 20, Folder 212)
  - Health, (Mental Health), 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 213)
  - Health, (Mental Health), 1971 (Box 20, Folder 214)
  - Health, (Mental Health), 1962-1968 (Box 20, Folder 215)
  - Health, Miscellaneous, 1970-1972 (Box 21, Folder 216)
  - Health, Miscellaneous, 1960-1969 (Box 21, Folder 217)
  - Health (Retarded, Autism, Clips), 1973 May-December (Box 21, Folder 218)
  - Health (Retarded, Autism, Clips), 1973 January-April (Box 21, Folder 219)
  - Health (Retarded, Autism, Willowbrook, NY), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 220)
  - Health (Retarded, Autism, Willowbrook, NY), 1972 (Box 21, Folder 221)
  - Health (Retarded, Autism, Willowbrook, NY), 1972 (Box 21, Folder 222)
  - Health (Retarded, Autism, Willowbrook, NY), 1962-1971 (Box 22, Folder 223)
  - Health (Rehabilitation, Workers Compensation), 1961-1962 (Box 22, Folder 224)
  - Herman, Pat (Freedom of the Press), 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 225)
  - Herman, Pat (Freedom of the Press), 1973 (Box 22, Folder 225A)
  - Hijacking, (Airlines-Middle East), 1970 (Box 22, Folder 226)
  - Hobart College (Thomas Tongyai-Undercover Agent) Geneva, New York, 1970 (Box 22, Folder 227)
  - Housing (See also UDC), 1969-1973 (Box 22, Folder 228)
  - Housing (See also UDC), 1961-1964 (Box 22, Folder 229)
  - Housing (Rent Control), 1971-1973 (Box 22, Folder 230)
  - Housing (Rent Control), 1960-1970 (Box 22, Folder 231)
  - Human Rights (Alabama-Georgia, Rev. Martin Luther King and Rev. Wyatt Tee Walker), 1965-1970 (Box 23, Folder 232)
  - Human Rights (Alabama-Georgia, Rev. Martin Luther King and Rev. Wyatt Tee Walker), 1961-1963 (Box 23, Folder 233)
  - Human Rights (John Bailey, Nelson A. Rockefeller), 1962 (Box 23, Folder 234)
  - Human Rights (Italians, Mafia, Columbo), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 235)
  - Human Rights (Jesse Jackson), 1971 (Box 23, Folder 236)
  - Human Rights (Jews, Anti-Semitism, JDL, Black Jewish Committee), 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 237)
  - Human Rights, Clarence Jones (Ghandi Society for Human Rights), 1963-1966 (Box 23, Folder 238)
  - Human Rights, Clarence Jones (Ghandi Society for Human Rights), 1961-1962 (Box 23, Folder 239)
  - Human Rights, Martin Luther King (Speech at Albany, New York), 1961 May 16 (Box 23, Folder 240)
  - Human Rights, Minister's Committee (Jobs), 1963-1964 (Box 23, Folder 241)
  - Human Rights, Miscellaneous, 1969-1973 (Box 23, Folder 242)
  - Human Rights, Miscellaneous, 1965-1966 (Box 23, Folder 243)
  - Human Rights, Miscellaneous, 1963 July-December (Box 23, Folder 244)
  - Human Rights, Miscellaneous, 1963 January-June (Box 23, Folder 245)
  - Human Rights, Miscellaneous, 1961-1962 (Box 24, Folder 246)
  - Human Rights, Miscellaneous, 1959-1960 (Box 24, Folder 247)
  - Human Rights, Mississippi, 1962-1966 (Box 24, Folder 248)
  - Human Rights, Jackie Robinson, 1966-1974 (Box 24, Folder 249)
  - Human Rights, Jackie Robinson, 1962-1965 (Box 24, Folder 250)
  - Human Rights, Walinsky Report (Official Lawlessness in New York State), 1969 (Box 24, Folder 251)
  - Human Rights, Walker, Wyatt (Urban Affairs), 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 252)
  - Human Rights, "We Remember Dr. Martin Luther King" Project, 1960-1969 (Box 24, Folder 253)